Guide to the Sterling Lord Papers MSS.058
Fales Library and Special Collections
Sterling Lord Papers
1946-2014
1952-1998
Fales Library and Special Collections
Lord, Sterling, 1920-
Sterling Lord Literistic Agency
MSS.058
441.5 Linear Feet in 436 record cartons, 3 manuscript boxes, and 3 oversize flat boxes.
Sterling Lord founded the Sterling Lord Agency in 1952 (later to become Sterling Lord Literistic). He has worked with well-known writers, such as Jack Kerouac, Ken Kesey, Anne Sexton, and the Berenstains. This collection contains Lord's professional papers, including financial records, contracts, correspondence, and subject files for the many authors he has worked with. Books and other print material represented by Sterling Lord are also included.
Scope and Content
This collection contains records created by Sterling Lord and the Sterling Lord Literistic Agency, including correspondence, manuscripts, photographs, promotional material, contracts, personnel files, financial records, and books and print material represented by the agency. The bulk of the collection comprises subject files of the authors who were managed by Sterling Lord and others at the agency. The collection covers a brief period of time before Sterling Lord founded the agency, and throughout the agency's operation, up to 2013.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into six series: Series I. Subject Files; Series II. Financial, Administrative, and Legal; Series III. Media; Series IV. May 2016 Accretion; Series V. June 2016 Accretions; and Series VI. Print Materials.
Series I, Subseries A: General subject files, is arranged chronologically by year, and alphabetically within each year. The rest of the collection is arranged alphabetically. Series IV and V have not been arranged by an archivist.
Conditions Governing Access
Donor permission is required for access. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Sterling Papers were was donated to NYU Libraries by Sterling Lord in two sections, in 1969 and 2010. In May of 2016 Paulina Calistru (on behalf of Sterling Lord) donated an addition to the collection. The accession number associated with this gift is 2016.024.
Biographical / Historical
Sterling Lord was born in Burlington, Iowa in 1920. He had an interest in tennis from a young age, and in high school became involved in sports journalism, calling in tennis scores to the local newspapers, and writing for his school newspaper. Lord's passion for tennis brought him to Grinnell College in Iowa. After college, he was drafted into the army, where he studied electronics and radar before being transferred to Europe. At the end of WWII, Lord started working for the European edition of "Stars and Stripes", an army publication. There he became the editor for "Weekend", a weekly magazine, which was shortly thereafter shut down by the army. Lord and Richard Evan Jones, the editor in chief, continued printing the magazine as a private enterprise, with offices in Frankfurt and, eventually, in Paris, where Lord met his wife, artist Dodie Yencesse. When "Weekend" folded in the late 1940's, Lord moved to New York City.
During his first two years in New York, Lord worked as an editor for three different magazines. Deciding that that the magazine industry was too unstable, Lord opened up a literary agency with partner Stanley Colbert in 1952. After a couple of years, Colbert left the agency and in 1954 it became the Sterling Lord Agency. During the early years of the agency, Lord mostly managed non-fiction and ghost writers, such as Charlie Samuels, John Keats, Rowland Barker and Al Hirshberg. That was also the period when he met, and started working with, Jack Kerouac. The agency grew quickly as Lord and the authors he published made names for themselves.
In 1987, Sterling Lord Agency merged with the firm Literistic, and has since continued to serve the literary community. Throughout the years, the Sterling Lord Literistic Agency has managed many well known authors such as Terry Southern, David Wise, Jimmy Breslin, Anne Sexton, Erica Jong, the Berenstain family, and many others.
Literary editors.; Literary agents.; Publishers and publishing |z United States |v Correspondence.; Jong, Erica; Sexton, Anne, 1928-1974; Southern, Terry; Zinsser, William, 1922-2015; Berenstain, Jan, 1923-2012; Berenstain, Stan, 1923-2005; Kerouac, Jack, 1922-1969; Kesey, Ken; Wise, David; Deford, Frank; Francis, Dick; Keats, John, 1920-2000; Naylor, Gloria; Fast, Howard, 1914-2003
- Series I: Subject Files
  Scope and Content
  This series contains the subject files kept by the Sterling Lord Literistic Agency. These files consist of correspondence of agents with authors and publishers. They also contain manuscripts, photographs, promotional material, and all other items associated with the authors being managed by the agency. Subseries A contains the general subject files. These are described at the box level. Subseries B contains subject files that had been removed by the agency, grouping the materials of specific authors together. There is still material from these authors in the general subject files.
  - Subseries A: General
    This subseries contains the general subject files from the Sterling Lord Archive. It includes correspondence files with authors, publishers, and agents, and other general subject files kept by Sterling Lord and other agents at the Sterling Lord Literistic Agency.
    - Correspondence - A - Farrell, 1953-1959 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence - Farrell - Heath, 1953-1959 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence - Hirshberg - Keats, 1953-1959 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence - Keats - Martin, 1953-1959 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence - Millard - Souvenir Press, 1953-1959 (Box 5)
    - Correspondence - Swanson - Yutang; General files - B, 1953-1959 (Box 6)
    - General files - B-G, 1953-1959 (Box 7)
    - General files - H-M, 1953-1959 (Box 8)
    - General files - M-S, 1953-1959 (Box 9)
    - General files - T-Z; Publishers - Abelard - Escapade, 1953-1959 (Box 10)
    - Publishers - Esquire - Oxford University Press, 1954-1959 (Box 11)
    - Publishers - Parade - Wyn, A.A.; France; Misc. - R, 1954-1959 (Box 12)
    - Misc. - S-Z; England - general, 1954-1959 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence - Aaronson - Daley, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence - Daly - Greenspan, 1958-1959 (Box 15)
    - Correspondence - Hano - Jarman, 1958-1959 (Box 16)
    - Correspondence - Johannson - Meany, 1958-1959 (Box 17)
    - Correspondence - Moore - Sneider, 1958-1962 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence - Sopkin - Wilson, 1958-1962 (Box 19)
    - Rejected authors - A-L, 1958-1962 (Box 20)
    - Rejected authors - M-Z; Correspondence - Aaron - Barry, 1958-1962 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence - Bell - Dabney, 1959-1962 (Box 22)
    - Correspondence - Davis - Glassman, 1959-1962 (Box 23)
    - Correspondence - Gloss - Hirsh, 1959-1962 (Box 24)
    - Correspondence - Hoffman - Kerouac, 1959-1962 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence - Kersh - Mittelholzer, 1959-1962 (Box 26)
    - Correspondence - Muller - Rogoff, 1959-1962 (Box 27)
    - Correspondence - Rose - Slater, 1959-1962 (Box 28)
    - Correspondence - Albert - Cocteau, 1960 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence - Cole - Hirshberg, 1960 (Box 30)
    - Correspondence - Hohenlohe - Parkinson, 1960 (Box 31)
    - Correspondence - Peacock - Torres, 1960 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - Torres - Zinsser; Misc.; Albert - Back, 1960-1961 (Box 33)
    - Correspondence - Barber - Daley, 1961 (Box 34)
    - Correspondence - Daly - Gubitz, 1961 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence - Hano - Levin, 1961 (Box 36)
    - Correspondence - Linn - Sims, 1961 (Box 37)
    - Correspondence - Skard - Yellin, Souvenir Press; Authors - A-E, 1961; 1962-1963 (Box 38)
    - Authors - F-W, 1962-1963 (Box 39)
    - Authors Y-Z; Rejected authors I-Z. Rejected author synopses A-Z, 1962-1963 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence - Aaron - Collin, 1963 (Box 41)
    - Correspondence - Condon - Gehman, 1963 (Box 42)
    - Correspondence - Gilman - Howland, 1963 (Box 43)
    - Correspondence - Howland - Keightley, 1963 (Box 44)
    - Correspondence - Kendall - Livingston, 1963 (Box 45)
    - Correspondence - Lloyd - Purdy, 1963 (Box 46)
    - Correspondence - Reardon - Southern, 1963 (Box 47)
    - Correspondence - Spain - Wurlitzer, 1963 (Box 48)
    - Correspondence - Wyden - Zinnser; General Correspondence - A-Z, 1963-1964 (Box 49)
    - ILM and Foreign Rights; Rejected Authors - A-Z, 1963-1964 (Box 50)
    - Nesbit Tearsheets - A-M, 1963-1966 (Box 51)
    - Nesbit Tearsheets - N-Z; International correspondence; Correspondence - Aaron - Ballantine, 1963-1966 (Box 52)
    - Correspondence - Barber - Dabney, 1964 (Box 53)
    - Correspondence - Daley - Glassman, 1964 (Box 54)
    - Correspondence - Goldberg - Hyams, 1964 (Box 55)
    - Correspondence - Inglis - Kiester, 1964 (Box 56)
    - Correspondence - Kitman - Noble, 1964 (Box 57)
    - Correspondence - Paxton - Smith, 1964 (Box 58)
    - Correspondence - Sneider - Von Effra, 1964 (Box 59)
    - Correspondence - Waber - Zinsser; Rejected Authors J-Z, 1964 (Box 60)
    - Client Correspondence - Adams - Commager, 1965 (Box 61)
    - Client Correspondence - Cook - Hirshberg, 1965 (Box 62)
    - Client Correspondence - Holmes - Koch, 1965 (Box 63)
    - Client Correspondence - Laram - Procter, 1965 (Box 64)
    - Client Correspondence - Purdy - Southern, 1965 (Box 65)
    - Client Correspondence - Southern - Zinsser, 1965 (Box 66)
    - General Correspondence - A-Z; Crawford Correspondence - A-R, 1965 (Box 67)
    - Crawford Correspondece - S-Z; Health Affairs Report; Nesbit Correspondence - A-G, 1965 (Box 68)
    - Nesbit Correspondence - G-N, 1965 (Box 69)
    - Nesbit Correspondence - P-Z; Rejected Authors - A-L, 1965-1966 (Box 70)
    - Rejected Authors - M-Z; Sterling Lord Personal; Correspondence A - Bird, 1965-1966 (Box 71)
    - Correspondence - Birmingham - Daly, 1966 (Box 72)
    - Correspondence - Davis - Granat, 1966 (Box 73)
    - Correspondence - Gratus - Jones, 1966 (Box 74)
    - Correspondence - Jones - Linn, 1966 (Box 75)
    - Correspondence - Loory - Purdy, 1966 (Box 76)
    - Correspondence - Q - Shields, 1966 (Box 77)
    - Correspondence - Shrake - Walton, 1966 (Box 78)
    - Correspondence - Warhol - Zinsser; General Correspondence - A-M, 1966 (Box 79)
    - General Correspondence - N-Z; Rejected Author Correspondence - A-I; Correspondence A - Bailey, 1966-1967 (Box 80)
    - Correspondence - Barber - Collier, 1967 (Box 81)
    - Correspondence - Commager - Fay, 1967 (Box 82)
    - Correspondence - Fleming - Hatcher, 1967 (Box 83)
    - Correspondence - Hein - Keats, 1967 (Box 84)
    - Correspondence - Kenner - Meyer, 1967 (Box 85)
    - Correspondence - Miller - Scanlon, 1967 (Box 86)
    - Correspondence - Schaap - Starnes, 1967 (Box 87)
    - Correspondence - Steadman - Walton, 1967 (Box 88)
    - Correspondence - Washburn - Zinsser; Rejected Authors - A-B, 1967-1969 (Box 89)
    - Rejected Authors - C-L, 1967-1969 (Box 90)
    - Rejected Authors - M-Z, 1967-1969 (Box 91)
    - Correspondence - C - Francis, 1973 (Box 92)
    - Correspondence - Critchfield - Green; A - Ashmore, 1975; 1980 (Box 93)
    - Correspondence - Astor - Conot, 1980 (Box 94)
    - Correspondence - Cooke - Fast, 1980 (Box 95)
    - Correspondence - Fast - Guttwillig, 1980 (Box 96)
    - Correspondence - H - Kilbourne, 1980 (Box 97)
    - Correspondence - King - Leonard, 1980 (Box 98)
    - Correspondence - Leavitt - Nelson, 1980 (Box 99)
    - Correspondence - New - Rodgers, 1980 (Box 100)
    - Correspondence - Rogers - Sirica, 1980 (Box 101)
    - Correspondence - Smyth - Wise, 1980 (Box 102)
    - Correspondence - Wool - Zousmer; A - Berenstain, 1980; 1981 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence - Berkowitz - Critchfield, 1981 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence - D - Fiske, 1981 (Box 105)
    - Correspondence - Fitzsimons - Gumpert, 1981 (Box 106)
    - Correspondence - H - Kaufman, 1981 (Box 107)
    - Correspondence - Keats - Leslie, 1981 (Box 108)
    - Correspondence - Levy - Packard, 1981 (Box 109)
    - Correspondence - Parfit - S, 1981 (Box 110)
    - Correspondence - Salinger - Thompson, 1981 (Box 111)
    - Correspondence - Todd - Wool, 1981 (Box 112)
    - Correspondence - Wren - Zousmer; A - Bograd, 1981; 1982 (Box 113)
    - Correspondence - Boyum - Colby, 1982 (Box 114)
    - Correspondence - Cole - Evans, 1982 (Box 115)
    - Correspondence - F - Greene, 1982 (Box 116)
    - Correspondence - Greenfield - Howington, 1982 (Box 117)
    - Correspondence - I - Kotz, 1982 (Box 118)
    - Correspondence - Kramer - Michaud, 1982 (Box 119)
    - Correspondence - Minus - Preiss, 1982 (Box 120)
    - Correspondence - Preston - Sexton, 1982 (Box 121)
    - Correspondence - Sexton - Vaughan, 1982 (Box 122)
    - Correspondence - W - Zousmer, 1982 (Box 123)
    - Correspondence - A - Berenstain, 1983 (Box 124)
    - Correspondence - Berenstain - Conot, 1983 (Box 125)
    - Correspondence - Conover - Fast, 1983 (Box 126)
    - Correspondence - Fast - Grillo, 1983 (Box 127)
    - Correspondence - Gross - Hunter, 1983 (Box 128)
    - Correspondence - I - Leonard, 1983 (Box 129)
    - Correspondence - Leslie - Multimedia, Inc., 1983 (Box 130)
    - Correspondence - N - R, 1983 (Box 131)
    - Correspondence - Radcliffe - Schweitzer, 1983 (Box 132)
    - Correspondence - Selby - Wade, 1983 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence - Wall - Zousmer, 1983 (Box 134)
    - Correspondence - A - Berenstain, 1984 (Box 135)
    - Correspondence - Berenstain - Califano, 1984 (Box 136)
    - Correspondence - Canfield - Dornberg, 1984 (Box 137)
    - Correspondence - Drew - Francis, 1984 (Box 138)
    - Correspondence - Franks - Gross, 1984 (Box 139)
    - Correspondence - Gross - Janeway, 1984 (Box 140)
    - Correspondence - Jennings - L, 1984 (Box 141)
    - Correspondence - Land - Michaelis, 1984 (Box 142)
    - Correspondence - Michaels - Pileggi, 1984 (Box 143)
    - Correspondence - Polk - S, 1984 (Box 144)
    - Correspondence - Sager - Silman, 1984 (Box 145)
    - Correspondence - Silver - W, 1984 (Box 146)
    - Correspondence - Wade - A, 1984; 1985 (Box 147)
    - Correspondence - Adair - Bensen, 1985 (Box 148)
    - Correspondence - Benson - C, 1985 (Box 149)
    - Correspondence - Caldwell - Denney, 1985 (Box 150)
    - Correspondence - Derdarian - Fiske, 1985 (Box 151)
    - Correspondence - Fitzgerald - Gould, 1985 (Box 152)
    - Correspondence - Grant - Holden, 1985 (Box 153)
    - Correspondence - Holland - Kaufman, 1985 (Box 154)
    - Correspondence - Keach - Lewis, 1985 (Box 155)
    - Correspondence - Linderman - Morris, 1985 (Box 156)
    - Correspondence - Morrow - Philipson, 1985 (Box 157)
    - Correspondence - Pick - Seglin, 1985 (Box 158)
    - Correspondence - Selby - Tobias, 1985 (Box 159)
    - Correspondence - Todd - Weschler, 1985 (Box 160)
    - Correspondence - Westin - Zousmer; A-B, 1985; 1986 (Box 161)
    - Correspondence - B - Bonnano, 1986 (Box 162)
    - Correspondence - Bools - Conover, 1986 (Box 163)
    - Correspondence - Consumer Federation of America - Ehrlich, 1986 (Box 164)
    - Correspondence - Eisenberg - Gillis, 1986 (Box 165)
    - Correspondence - Goldberg - Gross, 1986 (Box 166)
    - Correspondence - Gross - Hyperion, 1986 (Box 167)
    - Correspondence - I - Klein, 1986 (Box 168)
    - Correspondence - Kilnkenberg - M, 1986 (Box 169)
    - Correspondence - Machlowitz - Nightengale, 1986 (Box 170)
    - Correspondence - Nihmey - Puner, 1986 (Box 171)
    - Correspondence - Q - Samalin, 1986 (Box 172)
    - Correspondence - Sampson - Stern, 1986 (Box 173)
    - Correspondence - Stone - W, 1986 (Box 174)
    - Correspondence - Wall - Wyden, 1986 (Box 175)
    - Correspondence - X - Zollinger; A - Berenstain, 1986; 1987 (Box 176)
    - Correspondence - Berenstain - Carroll, 1987 (Box 177)
    - Correspondence - Chesire - Daly; G - Goodwin, 1987 (Box 178)
    - Correspondence - Goodwin - Hite, 1987 (Box 179)
    - Correspondence - Hohl - L, 1987 (Box 180)
    - Correspondence - Land - Morrow, 1987 (Box 181)
    - Correspondence - Morton - Rich, 1987 (Box 182)
    - Correspondence - Riisna - Summers, 1987 (Box 183)
    - Correspondence - Szollosi - Wyden, 1987 (Box 184)
    - Correspondence - X-Ziegler; A - Cosgrove, 1987; 1988 (Box 185)
    - Correspondence - D - Gardner, 1988 (Box 186)
    - Correspondence - Gent - Just, 1988 (Box 187)
    - Correspondence - K - Miller, 1988 (Box 188)
    - Correspondence - Morris - S, 1988 (Box 189)
    - Correspondence - S - Wise, 1988 (Box 190)
    - Correspondence - Wise - Z; A - Browne, 1988; 1989 (Box 191)
    - Correspondence - Buchwald - Ellsberg, 1989 (Box 192)
    - Correspondence - F - Greene, 1989 (Box 193)
    - Correspondence - Greene - Lewis, 1989 (Box 194)
    - Correspondence - Lord - Pierson, 1989 (Box 195)
    - Correspondence - Pileggi - Semler, 1989 (Box 196)
    - Correspondence - Shnayerson - Wise, 1989 (Box 197)
    - Correspondence - Wiseman - Z; A - Browne, 1989; 1990 (Box 198)
    - Correspondence - Bryan - Fast, 1990 (Box 199)
    - Correspondence - Fast - Gross, 1990 (Box 200)
    - Correspondence - H - Leonard, 1990 (Box 201)
    - Correspondence - Lewis - Parks, 1990 (Box 202)
    - Correspondence - Papa - S, 1990 (Box 203)
    - Correspondence - Salinger - Warga, 1990 (Box 204)
    - Correspondence - Webb - Ziegenmeyer, 1990 (Box 205)
    - Correspondence - A - Conover, 1991 (Box 206)
    - Correspondence - Cosgrove - Gardner, 1991 (Box 207)
    - Correspondence - Gavin - Kerouac, 1991 (Box 208)
    - Correspondence - Kerouac - Martin, 1991 (Box 209)
    - Correspondence - Meryman - Rooney, 1991 (Box 210)
    - Correspondence - Rothschild - Tlili, 1991 (Box 211)
    - Correspondence - Torme - Ziegenmeyer; A - Atwater, 1991; 1992 (Box 212)
    - Correspondence - B - Donaldson, 1992 (Box 213)
    - Correspondence - Donnell - Haber, 1992 (Box 214)
    - Correspondence - Hackley - Meryman, 1992 (Box 215)
    - Correspondence - Mooney - Rich, 1992 (Box 216)
    - Correspondence - Richardson - W, 1992 (Box 217)
    - Correspondence - Waite - Ziegenmeyer; A - Blakemore, 1992; 1993 (Box 218)
    - Correspondence - Boles - Ford, 1993 (Box 219)
    - Correspondence - Flood - Karney, 1993 (Box 220)
    - Correspondence - Karp - Parks, 1993 (Box 221)
    - Correspondence - Peters - Sampson, 1993 (Box 222)
    - Correspondence - Schanberg - Ulene, 1993 (Box 223)
    - Correspondence - V - Ziegenmeyer; A - Berenstain, 1993; 1994 (Box 224)
    - Correspondence - Berenstain - Drew, 1994 (Box 225)
    - Correspondence - Ducker - Gross, 1994 (Box 226)
    - Correspondence - H - McGinniss, 1994 (Box 227)
    - Correspondence - M - Q, 1994 (Box 228)
    - Correspondence - R - Summers, 1994 (Box 229)
    - Correspondence - T - Zakim; A - Atwater, 1994; 1995 (Box 230)
    - Correspondence - B - Braiker, 1995 (Box 231)
    - Correspondence - Brinkley - Douglas, 1995 (Box 232)
    - Correspondence - Drabinsky - Gardner, 1995 (Box 233)
    - Correspondence - Gent - Kerouac, 1995 (Box 234)
    - Correspondence - Kerouac - Lord, 1995 (Box 235)
    - Correspondence - Lord - Naylor, 1995 (Box 236)
    - Correspondence - New York Times - Reynolds, 1995 (Box 237)
    - Correspondence - Roach - Schaap; A - Berenstain, 1995; 1996 (Box 238)
    - Correspondence - Berenstain - Crockett, 1996 (Box 239)
    - Correspondence - D - Fitzgerald, 1996 (Box 240)
    - Correspondence - Flood - Kerouac, 1996 (Box 241)
    - Correspondence - Kerouac - Orban, 1996 (Box 242)
    - Correspondence - P - Saville, 1996 (Box 243)
    - Correspondence - Schaap - Streiber, 1996 (Box 244)
    - Correspondence - Streiber - W, 1996 (Box 245)
    - Correspondence - Walsh - Zakim, 1996 (Box 246)
    - Correspondence - A - Ewing, 1997 (Box 247)
    - Correspondence - F - Landmine, 1997 (Box 248)
    - Correspondence - Latham - Summers, 1997 (Box 249)
    - Correspondence - Summers - Z; A - Beach, 1997; 1998 (Box 250)
    - Correspondence - Berenstain - E, 1998 (Box 251)
    - Correspondence - Editor file - Kesey, 1998 (Box 252)
    - Correspondence - Kesey - Meekson, 1998 (Box 253)
    - Correspondence - Meisel - Sexton, 1998 (Box 254)
    - Correspondence - Summers - Z, 1998 (Box 255)
  - Subseries B: Compiled Author / Publisher Files
    This series contains subject files on authors, publishers, and agents at the Sterling Lord Literistic Agency. These files were separated from the general subject files by the agency.
    - Berenstains - A.J. Cossey Productions, 1989-1990 (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Berenstains - Ace Novelty, 1989-1991 (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - Berenstains - American Publication, 1982-1984 (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Berenstains - Andover Togo, 1993 (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Berenstains - Anna Concepts, 1991-1992 (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Berenstains - Antioch Limited, 1991-1993 (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Berenstains - Antioch Publishing, 1990-1993 (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Berenstains - Applause, 1988-1990 (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - Berenstains - Aviva Entertainment, 1982 (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - Berenstains - Betallic, Inc., 1993 (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - Berenstains - Block Drugs, 1989-1990 (Box 256, Folder 11)
    - Berenstains - "Books, Random House", Undated (Box 256, Folder 12)
    - Berenstains - Britanica Software, 1990-1993 (Box 256, Folder 13)
    - Berenstains - Brookfield Shoe, 1983-1985 (Box 256, Folder 14)
    - Berenstains - Budget Books, 1989-1992 (Box 256, Folder 15)
    - Berenstains - Carafiello Diehl, 1982-1991 (Box 256, Folder 16)
    - Berenstains - Cedar Fair / Cedar Point, 1983-1993 (Box 256, Folder 17)
    - Berenstains - Champion Productions, 1982-1983 (Box 256, Folder 18)
    - Berenstains - Chesapeake Consumer Products, 1990-1992 (Box 256, Folder 19)
    - Berenstains - Circle Fine Arts, 1992-1994 (Box 256, Folder 20)
    - Berenstains - Coleco Inc., 1982-1985 (Box 256, Folder 21)
    - Berenstains - Coleman Outdoor Products, 1993 (Box 256, Folder 22)
    - Berenstains - Collector Cars for Berenstain Bears, Undated (Box 256, Folder 23)
    - Berenstains - Collegeville Flag, 1981 (Box 256, Folder 24)
    - Berenstains - Connor Forest, 1983-1985 (Box 256, Folder 25)
    - Berenstains - Contenova Gifts, 1983-1985 (Box 256, Folder 26)
    - Berenstains - Creative Innovations, 1990-1991 (Box 256, Folder 27)
    - Berenstains - Deka Plastics, 1982-1984 (Box 256, Folder 28)
    - Berenstains - Ebeling and Reuss, 1981 (Box 256, Folder 29)
    - Berenstains - E. Glick Corp., 1983-1986 (Box 256, Folder 30)
    - Berenstains - Emotions / Mattel, 1983-1986 (Box 256, Folder 31)
    - Berenstains - Ero Industries, 1982-1984 (Box 256, Folder 32)
    - Berenstains - Fotozine, 1991 (Box 256, Folder 33)
    - Berenstains - Francisco Perona, 1983-1984 (Box 256, Folder 34)
    - Berenstains - Franco Manufacturing, 1983-1985 (Box 256, Folder 35)
    - Berenstains - Fun Lunch, 1984 (Box 256, Folder 36)
    - Berenstains - General Industries (A division of Nevitz Corp.), 1993 (Box 256, Folder 37)
    - Berenstains - General Merchandise, Undated (Box 256, Folder 38)
    - Berenstains - Gibson Greetings, 1988-1990 (Box 256, Folder 39)
    - Berenstains - Greeting Cards, Undated (Box 256, Folder 40)
    - Berenstains - Grolier Ent., 1984-1985 (Box 256, Folder 41)
    - Berenstains - H.H. Cutler, 1981 (Box 256, Folder 42)
    - Berenstains - Handley Printers, 1984-1985 (Box 256, Folder 43)
    - Berenstains - Harper Collins Royalty Statements, 1998 (Box 256, Folder 44)
    - Berenstains - Harper Collins Royalty Statements, 1998 (Box 256, Folder 45)
    - Berenstains - Hilasal, 1989-1991 (Box 256, Folder 46)
    - Berenstains - Home Decor, Undated (Box 256, Folder 47)
    - Berenstains - Imaizumi Co., 1983-1984 (Box 256, Folder 48)
    - Berenstains - Imperial Wall Coverings, 1989-1991 (Box 256, Folder 49)